Tufts University School of Medicine Yearbook UP150
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- School of Medicine Yearbook, 1924 -- 2020; UP150.001; 0.25 Linear Feet; 80 Volumes; 5757 Digital Object(s)
  - [School of Medicine yearbook], 1994; UP150.001.052.00001 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 115, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00118 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 116, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00119 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 117, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00120 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 118, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00121 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 119, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00122 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 120, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00123 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 121, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00124 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 122, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00125 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 123, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00126 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 124, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00127 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 125, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00128 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 126, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00129 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 127, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00130 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 128, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00131 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 129, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00132 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 130, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00133 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 131, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00134 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 132, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00135 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 133, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00136 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 134, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00137 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 135, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00138 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 136, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00139 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 137, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00140 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 138, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00141 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 139, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00142 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 140, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00143 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 141, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00144 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 142, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00145 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 143, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00146 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 144, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00147 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 145, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00148 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 146, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00149 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 147, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00150 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 148, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00151 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 149, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00152 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 150, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00153 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 151, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00154 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 152, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00155 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 153, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00156 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 154, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00157 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 155, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00158 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 156, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00159 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 157, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00160 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 158, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00161 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 159, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00162 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], page 160, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00163 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], inside back cover (1), 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00164 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], inside back cover (2), 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00165 (Volume 52)
    - [School of Medicine yearbook], back cover, 1994; UP150.001.052.00001.00166 (Volume 52)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995 [yearbook], UP150.001.053.00001 (Volume 53)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1995.
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, cover, UP150.001.053.00001.00001 (Volume 53)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1995
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 1, UP150.001.053.00001.00002 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 2, UP150.001.053.00001.00003 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 3, UP150.001.053.00001.00004 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 4, UP150.001.053.00001.00005 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 5, UP150.001.053.00001.00006 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 6, UP150.001.053.00001.00007 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 7, UP150.001.053.00001.00008 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 8, UP150.001.053.00001.00009 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 9, UP150.001.053.00001.00010 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 10, UP150.001.053.00001.00011 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 11, UP150.001.053.00001.00012 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 12, UP150.001.053.00001.00013 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 13, UP150.001.053.00001.00014 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 14, UP150.001.053.00001.00015 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 15, UP150.001.053.00001.00016 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 16, UP150.001.053.00001.00017 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 17, UP150.001.053.00001.00018 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 18, UP150.001.053.00001.00019 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 19, UP150.001.053.00001.00020 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 20, UP150.001.053.00001.00021 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 21, UP150.001.053.00001.00022 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 22, UP150.001.053.00001.00023 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 23, UP150.001.053.00001.00024 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 24, UP150.001.053.00001.00025 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 25, UP150.001.053.00001.00026 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 26, UP150.001.053.00001.00027 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 27, UP150.001.053.00001.00028 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 28, UP150.001.053.00001.00029 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 29, UP150.001.053.00001.00030 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 30, UP150.001.053.00001.00031 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 31, UP150.001.053.00001.00032 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 32, UP150.001.053.00001.00033 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 33, UP150.001.053.00001.00034 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 34, UP150.001.053.00001.00035 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 35, UP150.001.053.00001.00036 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 36, UP150.001.053.00001.00037 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 37, UP150.001.053.00001.00038 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 38, UP150.001.053.00001.00039 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 39, UP150.001.053.00001.00040 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 40, UP150.001.053.00001.00041 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 41, UP150.001.053.00001.00042 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 42, UP150.001.053.00001.00043 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 43, UP150.001.053.00001.00044 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 44, UP150.001.053.00001.00045 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 45, UP150.001.053.00001.00046 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 46, UP150.001.053.00001.00047 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 47, UP150.001.053.00001.00048 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 48, UP150.001.053.00001.00049 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 49, UP150.001.053.00001.00050 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 50, UP150.001.053.00001.00051 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 51, UP150.001.053.00001.00052 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 52, UP150.001.053.00001.00053 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 53, UP150.001.053.00001.00054 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 54, UP150.001.053.00001.00055 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 55, UP150.001.053.00001.00056 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 56, UP150.001.053.00001.00057 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 57, UP150.001.053.00001.00058 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 58, UP150.001.053.00001.00059 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 59, UP150.001.053.00001.00060 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 60, UP150.001.053.00001.00061 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 61, UP150.001.053.00001.00062 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 62, UP150.001.053.00001.00063 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 63, UP150.001.053.00001.00064 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 64, UP150.001.053.00001.00065 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 65, UP150.001.053.00001.00066 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 66, UP150.001.053.00001.00067 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 67, UP150.001.053.00001.00068 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 68, UP150.001.053.00001.00069 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 69, UP150.001.053.00001.00070 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 70, UP150.001.053.00001.00071 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 71, UP150.001.053.00001.00072 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 72, UP150.001.053.00001.00073 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 73, UP150.001.053.00001.00074 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 74, UP150.001.053.00001.00075 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 75, UP150.001.053.00001.00076 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 76, UP150.001.053.00001.00077 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 77, UP150.001.053.00001.00078 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 78, UP150.001.053.00001.00079 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 79, UP150.001.053.00001.00080 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 80, UP150.001.053.00001.00081 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 81, UP150.001.053.00001.00082 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 82, UP150.001.053.00001.00083 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 83, UP150.001.053.00001.00084 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 84, UP150.001.053.00001.00085 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 85, UP150.001.053.00001.00086 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 86, UP150.001.053.00001.00087 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 87, UP150.001.053.00001.00088 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 88, UP150.001.053.00001.00089 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 89, UP150.001.053.00001.00090 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 90, UP150.001.053.00001.00091 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 91, UP150.001.053.00001.00092 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 92, UP150.001.053.00001.00093 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 93, UP150.001.053.00001.00094 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 94, UP150.001.053.00001.00095 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 95, UP150.001.053.00001.00096 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 96, UP150.001.053.00001.00097 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 97, UP150.001.053.00001.00098 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 98, UP150.001.053.00001.00099 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 99, UP150.001.053.00001.00100 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 100, UP150.001.053.00001.00101 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 101, UP150.001.053.00001.00102 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 102, UP150.001.053.00001.00103 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 103, UP150.001.053.00001.00104 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 104, UP150.001.053.00001.00105 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 105, UP150.001.053.00001.00106 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 106, UP150.001.053.00001.00107 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 107, UP150.001.053.00001.00108 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 108, UP150.001.053.00001.00109 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 109, UP150.001.053.00001.00110 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 110, UP150.001.053.00001.00111 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 111, UP150.001.053.00001.00112 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 112, UP150.001.053.00001.00113 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 113, UP150.001.053.00001.00114 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 114, UP150.001.053.00001.00115 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 115, UP150.001.053.00001.00116 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 116, UP150.001.053.00001.00117 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 117, UP150.001.053.00001.00118 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 118, UP150.001.053.00001.00119 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 119, UP150.001.053.00001.00120 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 120, UP150.001.053.00001.00121 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 121, UP150.001.053.00001.00122 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 122, UP150.001.053.00001.00123 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 123, UP150.001.053.00001.00124 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 124, UP150.001.053.00001.00125 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 125, UP150.001.053.00001.00126 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 126, UP150.001.053.00001.00127 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 127, UP150.001.053.00001.00128 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 128, UP150.001.053.00001.00129 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 129, UP150.001.053.00001.00130 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 130, UP150.001.053.00001.00131 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 131, UP150.001.053.00001.00132 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 132, UP150.001.053.00001.00133 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 133, UP150.001.053.00001.00134 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 134, UP150.001.053.00001.00135 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 135, UP150.001.053.00001.00136 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 136, UP150.001.053.00001.00137 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 137, UP150.001.053.00001.00138 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 138, UP150.001.053.00001.00139 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 139, UP150.001.053.00001.00140 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 140, UP150.001.053.00001.00141 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 141, UP150.001.053.00001.00142 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 142, UP150.001.053.00001.00143 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 143, UP150.001.053.00001.00144 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 144, UP150.001.053.00001.00145 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 145, UP150.001.053.00001.00146 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 146, UP150.001.053.00001.00147 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 147, UP150.001.053.00001.00148 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 148, UP150.001.053.00001.00149 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 149, UP150.001.053.00001.00150 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 150, UP150.001.053.00001.00151 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 151, UP150.001.053.00001.00152 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 152, UP150.001.053.00001.00153 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 153, UP150.001.053.00001.00154 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 154, UP150.001.053.00001.00155 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 155, UP150.001.053.00001.00156 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 156, UP150.001.053.00001.00157 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 157, UP150.001.053.00001.00158 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 158, UP150.001.053.00001.00159 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 159, UP150.001.053.00001.00160 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, page 160, UP150.001.053.00001.00161 (Volume 53)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1995, back cover, UP150.001.053.00001.00162 (Volume 53)
  - Medical Yearbook, 1996; UP150.001.066 (Volume 66)
    Additional copy available in Reading Room.
  - Tufts University Medical School 1997 [yearbook], UP150.001.054.00001 (Volume 54)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1997.
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, cover, UP150.001.054.00001.00001 (Volume 54)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1997
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, title page, UP150.001.054.00001.00002 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 2, UP150.001.054.00001.00003 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 3, UP150.001.054.00001.00004 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 4, UP150.001.054.00001.00005 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 5, UP150.001.054.00001.00006 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 6, UP150.001.054.00001.00007 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 7, UP150.001.054.00001.00008 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 8, UP150.001.054.00001.00009 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 9, UP150.001.054.00001.00010 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 10, UP150.001.054.00001.00011 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 11, UP150.001.054.00001.00012 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 12, UP150.001.054.00001.00013 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 13, UP150.001.054.00001.00014 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 14, UP150.001.054.00001.00015 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 15, UP150.001.054.00001.00016 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 16, UP150.001.054.00001.00017 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 17, UP150.001.054.00001.00018 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 18, UP150.001.054.00001.00019 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 19, UP150.001.054.00001.00020 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 20, UP150.001.054.00001.00021 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 21, UP150.001.054.00001.00022 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 22, UP150.001.054.00001.00023 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 23, UP150.001.054.00001.00024 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 24, UP150.001.054.00001.00025 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 25, UP150.001.054.00001.00026 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 26, UP150.001.054.00001.00027 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 27, UP150.001.054.00001.00028 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 28, UP150.001.054.00001.00029 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 29, UP150.001.054.00001.00030 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 30, UP150.001.054.00001.00031 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 31, UP150.001.054.00001.00032 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 32, UP150.001.054.00001.00033 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 33, UP150.001.054.00001.00034 (Volume 54)
    - Tufts University Medical School 1997, page 34, UP150.001.054.00001.00035 (Volume 54)